Craig Seymour Collection, 1968-2006 SC 144
Archives of African American Music and Culture
- 2. Artist clippings
  - Outkast, 2001-2002 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    9 articles: A) Bozza, Anthony, "Outkast Let Their Freak Funk Fly," Rolling Stone, Nov. 23, 2000. B) Brunner, Rob, "Stankenstein," Entertainment Weekly, pp. 37-38, Nov. 10, 2000. C) Clover, Joshua, "The Future of Funk," GQ, pp. 169-175, Dec. 2000. D) Guzman, Isaac, "Melody Makers of Hip-Hop," Los Angeles Times, p. 8, Oct. 22, 2000. E) Jenkins, Sasha, "The End Of The Ice Age?," Spin, pp. 82-88, March 2001. F) Jones, Steve, "Outkast Signals Still More Success," USA Today, Nov. 3, 2000. G) Lowe, Todd Myers, "Outkast: Holiday in Stankonia," Alternative Press, pp. 52-28. H) Marriott, Rob, "Road Scholars," Vibe, pp. 144-154, March 16, 2001. I) Millner, Denene, "Hip Hop & Hot," Daily News, Nov. 4, 2000. J) Watson, Margeaux, "Something Smells Funky," Time Out New York, pp. 22-24, Nov. 2-9, 2000.
  - Outkast, 1999-2002 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Pendergrass, Teddy, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    Clippings + article. Faggins, Barbara, "Teddy's Transsexual Passenger Talks!," The Philadelphia Tribune, pp. 61-64, May 31, 1982.
  - Petrus, Jacques Fred, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Presley, Elvis, undated (Box 5, Folder 7)
    Robinson, Louie, "The Truth About That Elvis Presley Rumor: 'The Pelvis' Gives His Views on Vicious Anti-Negro Slur," Jet, pp. 58-61
  - Prince, 1979-2004 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    Clippings + comic book + article. Norment, Lynn, "Prince's Intriguing Women," Ebony, pp. 162-163, 166, 168, Nov. 1987.
  - Prince, 1990-2004 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    4 newspaper articles: A) Elie, Lolis Eric, "Prince Wins Fans Back With Soul," The Times Picayune, p. B-1, July 5, 2004. B) George, Nelson, "Whose Time Was It?," Voice, p. 70, 75, Sept. 11, 1990. C) Spera, Keith, "A Decade in the Dome," Lagniappe, pp. 22-23, 26, July 2, 2004. D) Spera, Keith, "Prince Holds Court At Essence Fest," The Times Picayune, p. A-21, July 4, 2004.
  - Queen Pen, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    2 articles: A) Alfano, Dino, "The Mighty Pen," Girlfriends, pp. 24-25, 42-43, July 1998. B) Rogers, Ray, "Out in America: The Mighty Pen," Out, pp. 63-64, April 1998.
  - Reid, L.A., 1996-2004 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    Clippings, notes, and 2 articles: A) Spruell, Sakina P., "King of Pop," Black Enterprise, pp. 95-96, Dec. 2000. B) "L.A. Reid Slam Dunked His 40th Birthday," Sister2Sister, pp. 6-12, Sept. 1996.
  - Reynolds, Jeannie, 1999-2000 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Reynolds, L.J., 2002 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Riperton, Minnie, 1978-1979 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    Article, clippings from Jet.
  - Robinson, Smokey, 2000-05-26 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    Sinclair, Tom, "Smokey Robinson," Entertainment Weekly, pp. 25-30
  - Rolling Stones, The, 1983-1989 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Ross, Diana, 1993-2003 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    Clippings + newspaper clippings + Musical Memoirs + article. Wielder, Judy, "Stop! In The Name of Love," The Advocate, pp. 32-40, May 11, 1999.
  - Rufus, undated (Box 5, Folder 18)
    Poster
  - Sanborn, David, undated (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Studdard, Ruben, 2003-08-21 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    Toure, "The People's Champ," Rolling Stone, pp. 44-50
  - Sylvester, 1979-1993 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    Clippings + 2 articles: A) Brownworth, Victoria A., "Black Out," The Advocate, p. 80, Aug. 13, 1992. B) Hewitt, Paolo, "Sylvester," New Musical Express, pp. 12-13, Dec. 1, 1984.
  - TLC, 1993-2005 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    Clippings + 2 articles: A) Mitchum, Jennifer, Interview, Sister2Sister, pp. 25-36, May 1999. B) Brown, Jamie Foster, "Congratualations Mommy T-Boz and Daddy Mack-10," Sister2Sister, pp. 58-71.
  - Toussaint, Allen, 1989-1998 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Usher, 1998-2005 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    Clippings + 2 articles: A) Brown, Jamie Foster, "Inside the Head of Usher," Sister2Sister, pp. 25-42, Nov. 2001. B) Talley, Jenell and Jennifer Mitchum, "Usher," Sister2Sister, pp. 36, 38-42, April 1998. Also includes complete issue of FHM, Spring/Summer 2005.
  - Vaughan, Sarah, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Warwick, Dionne, 1979-1984 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    Clippings + 3 articles: A) Hunt, Dennis, "340 Dionne Warwick Speaks Out For Strong Black Women," Ebony, pp. 95-100, May, 1983. B) "Dionne Warwick," Essence, pp. 85, 105-112. Oct. [year unknown]. C) Holden, Stephen, "Dionne Warwick Makes Herself Over," Rolling Stone, Nov. 15, 1979.
  - White, Barry, 1975-08-15 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    Lombardt, John, "Barry White: The Billy Jack Of Disco," Rolling Stone, pp. 53,56
  - Williams, Vanessa, 1994-08 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    Morgan, Joan, "Vanessa Williams: Soul Survivor," Essence, pp. 48-50, 116-118
  - Womack, Bobby, 1984-2001 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Wonder, Stevie, 2005-06 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    Complete issue of Uncut, June 2005.
  - Wright, Norma Jean, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Ying Yang Twins, 2005 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    Clippings + 5 articles: A) Peisner, David, "Reflection," Vibe, pp. 98-102, July 2005. B) Caramanica, Jon, "Seductive," XXL Magazine, pp. 94-96, 98-99, June 2005. C) Woods, Allen, "Quiet Riot," The Source, pp. 98-103, May 2005. D) Jones, Tiffany L., "U.S.A. United State of Atlanta," Black Men SSX, pp. 88-91, [unknown date]. E) Jones, Donovan, "How To Date Twins Simultaneously," King, June 2005.
- 3. Subject files
  - Atlanta, 1990-2005 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    Clippings + article. Murray, Sonia, "Welcome To Atlanta," Upscale, pp. 71-74, 77-92, 118, June/July 2002.
  - Atlanta -- Freaknik, 1994-2001 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Atlanta -- General, 1987-2003 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Atlanta -- LaFace, 1993-2003 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Atlanta -- The ATL Story (by Seymour), undated (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Atlanta -- publicity, undated (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Black culture & celebrity studies, 1992-2005 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    Misc. Clippings + 7 articles: A) (2 copies) Diawara, Manthia, "Black Studies, Cultural Studies: Performative Arts," AfterImage, pp. 6-8, Oct. 1992. B) Wanko, Cheryl, "Introduction," Roles of Authority, pp. 1-21, Texas Tech University Press. C) Garber, Marjorie, "Bisexuality and Celebrity," The Seductions of Biography, pp. 13-30, Routledge: New York; London. D) Rampersad, Arnold, "Psychology and Afro-American Biography," The Yale Review, pp. 1-18. E) Tate, Greg, "Above and Beyond Rap's Decibals," The New York Times, pp. 1, 38, March 6, 1994. F) Decker, Jeffrey Louis, "The State of Rap: Time and Place in Hip Hop Nationalism," Social Text, no. 34, pp. 53-84, 1993.
  - Black rock (Box 7, Folder 2)
    Spin article by David Browne, Village Voice article about Living Colour and black rock; Space Punk article
  - Blues, 1968-1978 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    5 essays: A) Garon, Paul, "Blues & The Poetic Spirit," New York: Da Cap Press, 1978. B) Olivier, Paul, "Screening The Blues: Aspects of the Bluse Tradition," New York: De Capo Press, 1968. C) (3 copies) Seymour, Craig, "Rereading The Blues."
  - Disco, 1975-2004 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Disco, 1976-1996 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    9 articles: A) Colacello, Bob, "Anything Went," Vanity Fair, pp. 182-196, March 1996. B) DJ Magazine, March 1993. C) Emerson, Ken, "The Village People: America's Male Ideal?," Rolling Stone, Oct. 5, 1978. D) Friedland, LeeEllen, "Disco: Afro-American Vernacular Performance," Dance Research Journal, pp. 27-35, 1983. E) Helgesen, Sally, "Disco," Harper's, pp. 20-24, Oct. 1977. F) Johnson, Herschel, "The Discotheque," Ebony, pp. 54-56, 58, 60, 62, Feb. 1977. G) Merritt, Jay, "Rock Strikes Back!," Rolling Stone, pp. 19, 23, March 20, 1980. H) Trillin, Calvin, "U.S. Journal: Boston: The Unpleasantness At Whimsey's," New Yorker, pp. 143-147, Dec. 13, 1976. I) Von Schilling, James, "Disco-mmunity, or I'm OK, You're OK, America's OK, So Let's Dance!," The Popular Culture Reader, ed. Jack Nachbar, Deborah Weiser, Jordan L. Wright, Bowling Green University Poplar Press, Bowling Green, OH. 1978.
  - Doo Wop, 2003 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    Unterberger, Richie, "Doo Wop," All Music Guide, 3 pgs, Allmusic.com.
  - Gospel & Go-Go, 1999-2003 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    3 articles: A) Hopkinson, Natalie, "Go-Go, And Sin No More," The Washington Post, p. C1, Aug. 27, 2002. B) Seymour, Craig, "A Singer Whose Size Fits Just Fine: Kelly Price, Beating Stereotypes," The Washington Post, pp. G1, G4, May 9, 1999. C) Wald, George, "From Spirituals to Swing: Sister Rosetta Tharpe and Gospel Crossover," American Quarterly, 55.3, 26 pgs, 2003.
  - Hip-Hop Soul, 1993-2004 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    Clippings + article. Hirschberg, Lynn, "Living Large," Vanity Fair, pp. 188-191, 233-239, Sept. 1993.
  - Rap, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    3 articles: A) George, Nelson, "In Defense of Rap--Gangsta or Not," Washington Post, G3, Feb. 20, 1994. B) Levy, Joe, "One or Two Things I Know About Gangsta," Voice Pazz & Jop, p. 11, March 1, 1994. C) Smith, Danyel, "Holler if You Hear Me," Voice Pazz & Jop, p. 20, March 1, 1994.
  - Rap -- Black Female, 1990-1993 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    Clippings + 3 articles: A) Jones, James T., "Female Rappers Go With The Gangsta Flow," USA Today, 6D, Oct. 5, 1993. B) Roberts, Robin, "Music Videos, Performance, and Resistance: Feminist Rappers," Journal of Popular Culture, pp. 141-152, vol. 25:2, Fall 1992. C) Wallce, Michele, "When Black Feminism Faces The Music, and the Music is Rap," The New York Times, July 29, 1990.
  - Rap -- Black Female, 1991-1993 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    5 newspaper articles: A) Christgau, Robert, "Rude Girls Rude," Voice, p. 76, July 13, 1993. B) George, Nelson, "Ladies First," Voice, pp. 69, 72, May 11, 1993. C) Jones, James T., "Female Rappers Go With The Gangsta Flow," USA Today, 6D, Oct. 5, 1993. D) Morgan, Joan, "Throw the 'F'," Voice, p. 75, June 11, 1991. E) Sarig, Roni & Neil Strauss, "Queen's New Castle," Village Voice, p.83, Sept. 28, 1993.
  - R&B Music/Performance, 1982-1999 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    Clippings + 2 articles: A) Futrell, Jon, et. al., The Illustrated Encyclopedia of Black Music, New York: Harmony Books, 1982. B) Seymour, Craig, "K-Ci & JoJo: Soul In the Key of Low," Washington Post, June 30, 1999.
  - R&B Music/Performance, 1989-1993 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    5 newspaper articles: A) Graham, Jefferson, "Jody Watley Makes a Stylish About-Face," USA Today, B) Jones, James T., "L.A. and Babyface, making Atlanta Center of Soul," USA Today, 4D, Feb. 22, 1993. C) Jones, James T., "Mavis Staples, Without Her Family of Singers," USA Today, 3D, Aug. 24, 1993. D) Pareles, Jon, "George Clinton Synthesizes 2 Decades of Funk," The New York Times, C14, July 19, 1989. E) Village Voice: Rock & Roll Quarterly, 5:3, Winter 1992.
  - Soul, 1972-1984 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    4 articles: A) Larkin, Rochelle, "The Soul Message," The Sounds of Social Change: Studies in Popular Culture, Eds. R. Serge Denisoff and Richard A. Paterson, Chicago: Rand McNally, 1972. B) Maultsby, Portia K., "Soul Music: Its Sociological and Political Significance in American Popular Culture," Journal of Popular Culture, Issue 17.2, Fall 1983. C) Stephens, Robert W., "Soul: A Historical Reconstruction of Continuity and Change in Black Popular Music," The Black Perspective in Music, vl. 12 #1, Spring 1984. D) Stewart, James B., "Relationships between Black Males and Females in Rhythm and Blues Music of the 1960s and 1970s," The Western Journal of Black Studies, Issue 3.3, Fall 1979.
  - Soul Train, 1973-09 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    Sharpe, Lynn, "Don Cornelius: Wizard of Soul," Encore, pp. 24-25, Sept. 1973
  - Uptown Records, undated (Box 7, Folder 16)
    Helligar, Jeremy, "The New R&B!," Vibe, pp. 94-100
  - The Wiz, 1978-1996 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Yu, Arlene -- Essay, 1988-03 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    "'I Was Born This Way': Celebrating Community in a Black Gay Disco," Radcliffe College, March 1988
- 4. Interviews
  - 4.1. Interviews related to Aaliyah
    - Aaliyah, 1 Audiocassette; Interview about the then-recent movie "Romeo Must Die." Interviewer not Craig Seymour, or possibly group interview with Seymour and other journalists.
      Shelf Number
      cass 2089 B
      Online Access
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/k61r46xk4h
    - Drexter, 1 Audiocassette; Interview about Aaliyah, her death, and the impact of her post-mortem video.
      cass 2128 A
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/b19f16jg1k
    - Michele Dix, 1 Audiocassette; Interview with Michele Dix (VP, Music and Talent Programming at MTV) discussing Aaliyah's post-mortem popularity.
  - 4.2. Interviews related to The B-52's
    - Cindy Wilson, 1 Audiocassette; Phone interview discussing meeting her husband at their first show, the early years of the B-52s, their album Cosmic Thing.
      cass 2107 A/B
      Existence and Location of Copies
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/n79h14h293
    - Keith Strickland, 1 Audiocassette; Discussion about the band's history, song-writing, Ricky Wilson's death, and the impact of The B-52's music within the gay community.
      cass 2095 A
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/r17188722k
  - 4.3. Interviews related to DJ Mandrill
    - DJ Mandrill, Seymour and Mandrill discuss Basement Jaxx.
      General
      cass 2448 A
      Related Materials
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/v23v83fj4j
    - DJ Mandrill, 1999-05-14; 1 Audiocassette; In-person interview with DC-based DJ Mandrill about the black gay community, gospel, hip hop, dance music.
      cass 2082 A; cass 2153 A
      cass 2082 A: https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/k41z40s66k
      cass 2153 A: https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/c67w62mj4j
      Interview content is duplicated between cass 2082 and cass 2153.
  - 4.4. Interviews related to Dru Hill
    - Dru Hill, 1 Audiocassette; In-person interview with members of the R&B group Dru Hill about their work, recording/arranging process, etc.
      cass 2118 A/B
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/q67j72vp4g
    - [Kevin Peck?], 1 Audiocassette; [Kevin Peck?] (manager for Dru Hill) discussing controversy surrounding Dru Hill, Sisqo, etc.
      cass 2117 B
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/484z50p46m
  - 4.5. Interviews related to En Vogue
    - Amanda Cole, 1 Audiocassette; Telephone interview, discusses joining En Vogue as Maxine Jones left En Vogue.
      cass 2073 A
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/r56n00h26c
    - Cindy Herron, 1 Audiocassette; Phone interview with Herron about continuing En Vogue after Dawn Robinson and Maxine Jones' departure from the group.
      cass 2131 A/B
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/197x61m029
    - Dawn Robinson, 3 Audiocassettes; In-person interview with Dawn Robinson, an unidentified acquaintance, and some family members discussing the promotional tour for her new album, being a member of and leaving En Vogue, and related topics.
      cass 2065 A/B; cass 2135 A/B; cass 2099 A/B
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/b39722pq89
    - En Vogue, circa 2000; 1 Audiocassette; Telephone interview with Terry Ellis, Cindy Herron, and Maxine Jones of En Vogue about their 2000 album Masterpiece Theatre.
      cass 2075 A
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/t74c682z79
    - Maxine Jones, 1 Audiocassette; On her time with and departure from En Vogue, Dawn Robinson's solo work.
    - Rico Wade, 1 Audiocassette; Rico Wade (of Organized Noize, a hip hop production company) discussing En Vogue's "Don't Let Go" single.
      cass 2119 A
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/j03c97s401
    - Sylvia Rhone, 1 Audiocassette; Sylvia Rhone (CEO at Elektra) discussing her public feud with Dawn Robinson of En Vogue.
      cass 2119 B
    - Terry Ellis, circa 2001; 1 Audiocassette; Telephone interview about the departure of Dawn and Maxine and the future of En Vogue.
      cass 2078 A/B
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/s95643h80w
  - 4.6. Interviews related to Jaheim
    - Jaheim, 2 Audiocassettes; In-person interview with singer Jaheim Hoagland discussing his early albums and career, his time in prison, his family, his work.
      cass 2115 A/B; cass 2160 A
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/f85n306139
    - Kaygee, 1 Audiocassette; Telephone interview about Kaygee's work with Jaheim.
      cass 2127 A
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/v33r86hh5b
    - Kevin Owens, 1 Audiocassette; Telephone interview about Jaheim and Luther Vandross.
    - T.D. Hoagland, 1 Audiocassette; Telephone interview about Jaheim's early life and career.
  - 4.7. Interviews related to Janet Jackson
    - Janet Jackson, 2 Audiocassettes; In-person interview with Janet Jackson on an airplane about her work, her recent relationship (early 2000s?), Paula Abdul, etc.
      cass 2092 A; cass 2098 A/B
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/742930j80j
    - Janet Jackson, 1 Audiocassette; In-person interview with Janet Jackson [and one of her producers, possibly Jimmy Jam?] about various topics.
      cass 2121 A
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/w92435np5g
    - Janet Jackson, 1 Audiocassette; In-person interview with Janet Jackson about fame, her work, personal life, etc. Jimmy Jam briefly joins the conversation.
      cass 2150 A/B
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/c28950b90b
  - 4.8. Interviews related to Joi
    - Dallas Austin, 1 Audiocassette; Interview about Joi's album Star Kitty's Revenge and her influence on the Atlanta music scene.
      cass 2152 A
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/940791zj3d
    - Joi (Joi Gilliam), 1 Audiocassette; Interview with Joi (Joi Gilliam) dicussing her Honey cover appearance, her upcoming concert in Atlanta.
      cass 2128 B
    - [Raphael Saadiq?], 1 Audiocassette; Interview about Joi's album Star Kitty's Revenge and her influence on the Atlanta music scene.
    - [?] Vaughn (disc jockey at KMEL?), 1 Audiocassette; Interview about Joi's album Star Kitty's Revenge and her influence on the Atlanta music scene.
    - [Unidentified Universal record exec], 1 Audiocassette; Interview about Joi's album Star Kitty's Revenge and her influence on the Atlanta music scene.
  - 4.9. Interviews related to Lauryn Hill
    - Andrea Martin, 1998?; 1 Audiocassette; Telephone interview with R&B singer/producer Andrea Martin about Lauryn Hill and her own work
      cass 2072 A
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/d375844151
    - Drew Dixon, circa 1998; 1 Audiocassette; Phone interview with Drew Dixon (former VP of A&R at Arista Records) discussing [Lauryn Hill?] and her work as a producer, black female producers in general.
      cass 2110 A
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/821g553p3h
    - Drew Dixon, circa 1998; 1 Audiocassette; Phone interview with Drew Dixon about her work with Lauryn Hill.
      cass 2123 B
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/494v53rj2f
    - Iyanla Vanzant?, 1998?; 1 Audiocassette; Telephone interview with author and talk show host Iyanla Vanzant about Lauryn Hill and R&B
    - Kelly Price, circa 1998; 1 Audiocassette; Phone interview with Kelly Price about Lauryn Hill's work and success.
      cass 2110 B
    - Lauryn Hill, circa 1998; 1 Audiocassette; Phone interview with Lauryn Hill about her career, collaborations, etc.
      cass 2123 A/B
    - Lil' Mo, 1998?; 1 Audiocassette; Telephone interview with rapper Lil' Mo (Cynthia Loving) about Lauryn Hill
      cass 2072 B
    - Mary Cutrufello, 1998?; 1 Audiocassette; Telephone interview with singer/songwriter Mary Cutrufello discussing Lauryn Hill, her recent album [Songs from the 6?]
    - Maurice Devoe, 1998?; 1 Audiocassette; Telephone interview with WPGC 95.5 disc jockey Maurice Devoe on Hill's song "To Zion" and her work
    - Nikki [Bratcher], circa 1998; 1 Audiocassette; Phone interview with Nikki [Bratcher] from R&B group Divine discussing Lauryn Hill and her own work.
  - 4.10. Interviews related to LGBTQ issues on college campuses
    - Charles Stephens (Morehouse student), 1 Audiocassette; Phone interview with some students discussing an early GLBT organizations, GLBT policy, incidents of violence against GLBTs at HBCUs, possible discussion of Howard and Johnson C. Smith universities.
      cass 2091 A
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/356910r013
    - Craig Washington, 1 Audiocassette; Craig Washington (essayist and public speaker) discusses the black gay community, beating incident at Morehouse, etc. with Seymour.
      cass 2146 A/B
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/079524qv4g
    - Gerald Wilson, 2002; 1 Audiocassette; Interview via telephone with gay student at Morehouse College discsses the same beating incident as above. Also in late 2002. [Second interview on TP84A?]
      cass 2071 B
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/989r07b62z
    - Gerald Wilson, 2002; 1 Audiocassette; Phone interview about gay life at Morehouse, violence on campus. Gives phone #s for other GLBT students on campus towards end of interview;.
      cass 2145 A
    - Jude [?], 1 Audiocassette; Telephone interview, former Morehouse student discusses gay activism at Morehouse, response to the 2002 beating [see TP10]
      cass 2079 A
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/k61r46xk5t
    - Jude [?], 1 Audiocassette; Phone interview about an anti-gay incident on the Morehouse campus [previous interview with same subject, see cass 2079].
      cass 2090 B
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/p68k424v4g
    - Larry and Bryan, 2002; 1 Audiocassette; Two students at Morehouse College discuss a recent incident where a gay student was beaten with a baseball bat. In-person interview in late 2002.
      cass 2071 A/B
    - Marion Harvey and Craig Stewart, 1 Audiocassette; Authors of the play A Day (In The Life), in-perons interview discussing their play that deals with issues of sexuality and race and HIV
    - Robert Arnold, 1 Audiocassette; "Robert, school stuff"- phone interview with Robert Arnold, student at Morehouse, about an anti-gay incident on campus.
      cass 2090 A
    - Susan [?], 1 Audiocassette; National Gay Lesiban Task Force Member, phone interview about the NGLTF survey of GLBT climate on college campuses
    - Unidentified actor, 1 Audiocassette; An actor in A Day (In The Life), in-person interview, discusses his role, his activism at Morehouse
      cass 2079 B
    - Unidentified board member of Council for the Advancement of Standards in Higher Education, 1 Audiocassette; Discusses their organization's engagement with campus faculty and staff to inform about LGBTQ issues and develop ways to support students.
    - Unidentified interviewee, 1 Audiocassette; Discusses homophobic incidents on college campuses and an event that took place to discuss and organize support.
      cass 2090 A/B
    - Unidentified man [Sterling Washington?], 1 Audiocassette; A founder of the Bisexual Lesbian and Gay Organization of Students at Howard, telephone interview about GLBT issues on campus.
    - Unidentified Morehouse student, 1 Audiocassette; Phone interview with some students discussing an early GLBT organizations, GLBT policy, incidents of violence against GLBTs at HBCUs, possible discussion of Howard and Johnson C. Smith universities.
    - Unidentified officer of BLAGOSA at Morehouse Univ, 1 Audiocassette; Phone interview discussing the climate for GLBT students Howard, Morehouse, etc.
  - 4.11. Interviews related to Lil' Mo
    - DJ Clue, 1 Audiocassette; Brief interview with [DJ Clue?].
      cass 2149 A
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/d56z908990
    - Lil' Mo, circa 2000; 1 Audiocassette; In-person interview with Lil' Mo (Cynthia Loving) about her success with "Superwoman," early work, fame.
      cass 2064 A/B
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/p38w32xh6r
    - Lil' Mo, 1 Audiocassette; Recording of Lil' Mo performing at a club [in DC?], followed by an in-person interview with Lil' Mo.
    - Lil' Mo, 1 Audiocassette; In-person interview with Lil' Mo (Cynthia Loving).
      cass 2122 A